BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VI: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
  - Code no.570670: Union Carbide Corporation and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-58, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Code no.580154: Printing Plates, Inc. and Toledo Photo-Engravers' Union, Local 15-P, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Code no.580154: Siedel-Farris and Clark, Inc. and Toledo Photo-Engravers' Union, Local 15-P, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Code no.580154: Toledo Engraving Company and Toledo Photo-Engravers' Union, Local 15-P, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Code no.541552: American Zinc Company of Illinois and International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 82, 1964- 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Code no.550555: United States Borax and Chemical Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1124, 1962- 1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Code no.550556: United States Borax and Chemical Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Crafts Local 1912, 1962- 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Code no.550557: United States Borax and Chemical Corporation and United Stone and Allied Products Workers of America, Local 179, 1962- 1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Code no.551039: NVF Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 487, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Code no.551079: McPhillips Manufacturing Company, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 1932, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Code no.551265: Dunlop Tire and Rubber Corporation and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 135, 1965- 1967 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Code no.551477: Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 164, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Code no.551478: Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 287, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Code no.551476: Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 12, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Code no.551479: Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union Local 200, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Code no.551480: Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 176, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Code no.551481: Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 50, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Code no.551644: Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers Local 378, 1965- 1967 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Code no.551732: Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 313, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Code no.551733: Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 80, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Code no.551734: Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 33, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Code no.551981: Medusa Portland Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers' Local 81, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Code no.551980: Manitowoc Portland Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers, Local 34, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Code no.551982: Medusa Portland Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers Local 173, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Code no.551983: Medusa Portland Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers, Local 175, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Code no.552316: Franklin Association of Chicago and Paper Rulers' Protective Association No. 26, 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Code no.560077: Georgia-Pacific Corporation and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 2661, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Code no.560534: F.N. Burt Co., Inc. and International Association of Machinists, District 76, Lodge 675, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Code no.560866: National Carbide Co. and International Chemical Workers' Union, Local 382, 1956-1967 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Code no.561521: Inland Container Corporation and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 954, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Code no.561708: American Zinc Oxide Company and International Chemical Workers, Local 368, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Code no.561793: S.D. Warren Company and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 954, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Code no.561793: S.D. Warren Company and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 136, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Code no.561910: Weyerhaeuser Company, Whittier Branch and Printing Specialties and Paper Products, Local 388, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Code no.550425: American Olean Tile Co., Inc. and United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, Local 151, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Code no.550863: W.R. Grace and Co. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 9-434, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Code no.551115: U.S. Plywood Corporation and International Woodworkers of America, Locals, 3-244, 3-246, 1965-1972 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Code no.551404: Alpha Portland Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 388, 1965- 1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Code no.551405: Alpha Portland Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 186, 1965- 1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Code no.551406: Alpha Portland Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 53, 1965- 1967 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Code no.551407: Alpha Portland Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 43, 1965- 1967 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Code no.551408: Alpha Portland Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 21, 1965- 1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Code no.551409: Alpha Portland Cement Company and United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 7, 1965- 1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Code no.551645: Georgia-Pacific Corporation and International Woodworkers of America, Local 5-475, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Code no.551889: Art Color Printing Company and Dunellen Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union, Local 316, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Code no.552058: Osborn-Midwest Paper Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Locals 322, 428, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Code no.552131: Linear, Inc. and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, CIO, Local 204, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Code no.552243: Eureka Fire Brick Works, Hot Tops Inc. and United Brick and Clay Workers of America, Local 530, 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Code no.552269: Glaziers of America and Glass Warehouse Workers and Paint Handlers, Local 206, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Code no.560248: Reliance Panelyte, Inc. and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 433, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Code no.560284: North American Refractories Company and United Brick and Clay Workers of America, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Code no.560333: Paper Box Companies, Los Angeles, California and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 307, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Code no.560649: Louie Glass Company and Progressive Glassworkers Union, Local 1, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Code no.561308: Texaco, Inc. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-638, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Code no.561447: Cities Service Oil Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 4-500, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Code no.561448: Cities Service Oil Company and Office Employees International Union, Local 87, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Code no.561450: Cities Service Oil Company and Lake Charles Metal Trades Council, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Code no.570023: E.I. Du Pont De Nemours and Co. and Fabrikoid Works Employees' Association, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Code no.551063: Iroquois China Company and United Mine Workers of America, District 50, Local 12860, 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Code no.551362: Recto Molded Products, Inc. and International Molders and Allied Workers, Local 4, 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Code no.560150: Lily-Tulip Cup Corporation and Printing Specialties and Paper Products, Local 470, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Code no.560662: Socony Mobil Oil Company, Inc. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 4-208, 1964- 1966 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Code no.561489: Art Color Printing Company and Dunellen Flymen's Union 373, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Code no.561789: Telegraph Press and International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, Local 115, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Code no.561789: Stackpole Company and International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, Local 115, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Code no.561825: W.R. Grace and Co., Davison Chemical Division and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 39, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Code no.570589: Philips Petroleum Company, Cactus Plant and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Code no.570737: International Paper Company, Long-Bell Division and Plywood and Veneer Workers, Local 2524, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Code no.571144: Georgia-Pacific Corporation and International Woodworkers of America, Local 3-2683, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Code no.541108: Associated Printing Industries, Union Shop Division and Bookbinders' and Bindery Women's Union, No. 31-125, 1964- 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Code no.550353: Contract Employers of the Graphic Arts Institute of New England, Inc. and Boston Press Assistants' Union, Local 18, 1964- 1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Code no.550913: California Oil Company, Western Division and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 552, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Code no.552195: U.S. Phosphoric Products and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 439, 1965-1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Code no.560285: Keyport Plant of Armstrong Cork Company and Federal Labor Union, Local 22703, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Code no.560700: American Cyanamid Company and United Mine Workers of America, Local 12037, District 50, 1965-1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Code no.561445: Hercules Inc., Imperial Color and Chemical Department and United Mine Workers of America, Local 12692 - International Union of District 50, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Code no.561512: Harbison-Walker Refractories Company and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Code no.561801: Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company, Chemical Division and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1317, 1966- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Code no.570027: H.K. Porter Company, Inc. and International Chemical Workers Union, Local 295, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Code no.570613: E.R. Squibb and Sons, Inc. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-138, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Code no.570622: Wilson H. Lee Company and New Haven Typographical Union, Local 47, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Code no.570803: New London Mills, New London, CT and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 462, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Code no.571124: S.D. Warren Company and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 1015, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Code no.571188: Art Color Printing Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 167, 1967- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Code no.520000: Fibreboard Corporation, Portland, Oregon Plant and Construction and General Laborers' Union, Local 320, 1967- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Code no.580087: Chapman and Dewey Lumber Co. and International Woodworkers of America, Local 5-344, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Series VII: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.550969: Sylvania Electric Products, Inc. and International Union of Electrical, Ratio and Machine Workers, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Code no.551497: Simplex Wire and Cable Co. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1262, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Code no.551747: Western Partition Corporation and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 307, 1964- 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Code no.551797: Sylvania Electric Products, Inc., Hicksville Plant and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, Local 8-149, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Code no.552003: Standard-Thomson Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Local 1836, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Code no.552245: Dayton Malleable Iron Company, G.H.R. Foundry Division and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 765, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Code no.560004: Dravo Corporation and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Lodge 582, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Code no.560026: California Metal Trades Association and East Bay Automotive Machinists Lodge 1546, Local 1176, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Code no.560465: Vendo Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Code no.560509: Industrial Relations Council of Furniture Manufacturers in Southern California and Furniture Workers Union, Local 3161, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Code no.560744: Chicago Hardware Foundry Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1192, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Code no.560766: Kroehler Mfg. Co. and International Woodworkers of America, Local 5-51, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Code no.560776: Sparco Wire Company and Mechanics Educational Society of America, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Code no.561010: Davis and Thompson Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Code no.561056: Connecticut Coke Company and International Union of District 50, United Mine Workers of America, Local 12000, 1966- 1968 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Code no.561236: Mesara-Cliffs Mining Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Code no.561274: Green River Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 6469, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Code no.570276: Esterbrook Pen Company and Industrial Union of Pen and Pencil Workers, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Code no.540562: Magnavox Company and Allied Industrial Workers of America, Local 254, 1961-1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Code no.550135: Colt's Inc. and Amalgamated Local 376, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Code no.550115: American Smelting and Refining Company and International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 625, 1964- 1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Code no.550359: Phelps Dodge Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Code no.550454: Inspiration Consolidated Copper Company and International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 586, 1964- 1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Code no.550483: Magma Copper Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 570, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Code no.550846: Perfect Circle Corporation and Hagerstown Independent Piston Ring Workers Union, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Code no.550897: Cinch Manufacturing Company and United Industrial Workers of America, Local 300, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Code no.551862: Conmar Products Corporation and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 454, 1965- 1971 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Code no.552005: McCord Corporation and International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America, Local 638, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Code no.560249: Standard Kollsman Industries, Inc. and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 1003, 1964- 1967 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Code no.560280: Retail Furniture Association of Milwaukee, Wisconsin and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 444, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Code no.560745: Columbus Auto Parts Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers, Local 30, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Code no.560901: SCM Corporation, Data Processing Systems Division and Tool and Die Craftsmen, National Federation of Independent Unions, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Code no.561279: Vitro Electronics, Division of the Vitro Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1762, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Code no.561433: New York Shipbuilding Corporation and Marine Draftsmen's Association, Local 209, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Code no.561471: Kennecott Copper Corporation, Chino Mines Division and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Code no.570551: South Florida Sign Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 349, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Code no.540536: Electric Products Company and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 728, 1969- 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Code no.550033: Dodge Manufacturing Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1191, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Code no.550151: Fedders Corporation and International Union of Electrical Workers, Local 413, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Code no.550665: ESCO Corporation and Esco Employees Association, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Code no.550871: Chris-Craft Corporation and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 2392, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Code no.550999: Rockwood Sprinkler Company and Rockwood Sprinkler Company Employees, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Code no.551555: Ladish Co. and Associated Unions of America, Office and Professional Workers, Local 85, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Code no.551697: Appliance Service Firms and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 76, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Code no.551916: Caldwell Foundry and Machine Co. and International Molders and Allied Workers Union, Local 255, 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Code no.552211: Jubilee Manufacturing Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 3092, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Code no.560060: Joseph T. Ryerson and Son, Inc. and Teamsters Local 135 of Indianapolis, Indiana, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Code no.560258: Acme Cotton Products Co., Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Code no.560307: Parker-Kalon Fasteners and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 177, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Code no.560406: Corona Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL, Local 3, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Code no.560459: Unit Crane and Shovel Corporation, Bay City Division and United Steelworkers of America, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Code no.560819: I-T-E Circuit Breaker Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1063, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Code no.560840: Valve Corporation of America and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 238, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Code no.560943: Hedstrom Union Company and United Furniture Workers of America, Local 154, 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Code no.560978: Haywood Manufacturing Company, Inc. and Haywood Shop Employees Association, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Code no.570056: Fleetwood Trailer Co., Inc. and San Bernardino-Riverside Counties District Council, Local 1959, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Code no.570060: Mobile Holdings Corporation and Orange County District Council of Carpenters, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Code no.540087: United Aircraft Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 700, 1962-1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Code no.551564: Goodyear Aerospace Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodges 49 and 763, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Code no.551828: General Dynamics and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 90, 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Code no.552124: Electronics Division of Sparton Corporation and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 666, 1963-1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Code no.560486: North American Aviation, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 260, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Code no.560518: Red Roller Bit Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 2083, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Code no.560582: Arnold, Schwinn and Company and Schwinn Employees Shop Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Code no.560633: Sylvania Electric Products, Inc., Wheeling Plant and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1724, 1965- 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Code no.560719: Rome Cable Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 1875, 1966- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Code no.561050: North American Aviation, Inc. and Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America, District Council of Painters, No. 36, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Code no.561838: Johnson Motors and Independent Marine and Machinists Association, Local 1, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Code no.561848: Page Aircraft Maintenance, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Lodge 2003, 1966- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Code no.561870: United Aircraft Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Hartford Aircraft Lodge 743, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Code no.561898: International Harvester Company, Solar Division and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 569, 1966- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Code no.561915: North American Aviation, Inc. and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Code no.561917: North American Aviation, Inc. and United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 770, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Code no.561918: North American Aviation, Inc., Clear Lake Facility and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Code no.561920: North American Aviation, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 89, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Code no.561922: North American Aviation, Inc., Rocketdyne Division and International Union, United Plant Guard Workers of America, Local 99, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Code no.570202: Dredge Employers, Great Lakes Region and Inland boatmen's Union, Seafarers' International Union, Atlantic, Gulf, Lakes and Inland Waters District, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Code no.570437: Alco Products, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 3180, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Code no.570448: North American Aviation, Inc. and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Code no.580046: United Aircraft Corporation, Norden Division and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 244, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 66)